

JESÚS MUÑOZ

Web Developer & Customer Support

PROFILE

With six years of experience in customer service and client support, I have developed strong skills in onboarding, training, troubleshooting, and customer engagement.

Additionally, my three years in software development make me a unique candidate, allowing me to better understand customer needs and achieve objectives more efficiently.

CONTACT

+34 655 661 558

jesusmunozpost@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jesus-munnoz-post

jesusmunnoz.github.io

Rúa Rosalía de Castro, Vigo

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native

English Professional (C1)

French Basic (B1)

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP (2024 - 2024) Codenotch

Fullstack web developer

DEGREE(2012 - 2016) Universidad Camilo José Cela

FORMACIÓN PROFESIONAL (2008 - 2010) Universidad Francisco de Vitoria

X-Ray Technician

Video Game Design

EXPERIENCE

Codenotch (jul-sep 2024)

· Web developer

Fullstack web developer. Web design usign HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL.

Carrefour (may-nov 2023)

BackEnd developer

Cash machine software developer. Development using C/C++.

Align Technology (oct 2018 - may 2023)

• Clinical Application Specialist / CAD Designer

Development using C/C++.

Develop and communicate the new generation of treatments with doctors.

Onboard new customer.

3D Smile Designer.

Teach, train, and support our customer.

Support and translator for various locations in Europe.

Tecnatom (nov 2017- oct 2018)

Unity 3D Developer

E- learning app developer for the nuclear industry. Development using C#.

3D designer using Autodesk 3D Max

Hospital Ntra. Sra. de america (oct 2010-oct 2012)

X-Ray Technician

Collaborated with a dynamic team in the Radiology, Mammography, and Operating Theater departments, contributing to the seamless operation of medical imaging services.